It's harder to do. There's more energy needed,
more focus needed on this task,
and I know from experience.
And I also know
from comments on my YouTube channel that it's it's often
the case
when you start something that is a little bit more
difficult,
and then you think, ah,
this
is too hard. I can't do it.
Let's
just listen to a podcast episode instead.
Or let's just go on YouTube and see what videos
are available.
Right now and I do this too,
so if I'm trying to focus on something with my
work,
it's a little bit difficult.
I'll switch the tab and just check my emails or
I'll check out the YouTube tab and see,
oh, it's something new there,
what what can ever look at where I pick up
my phone and check my emails so this is a
big problem and I think it's actually getting worse.
I'll leave a link to my video where I talk
about social media and how addictive it can be.
And how it just takes away our focus.
A lot of the time,
but the concept I really want to talk about today
is to embrace the difficulty.
So this means to really get excited,
OK, excited about when something is a little bit too
difficult for you,
or when something seems quite hard to do.
And the main reason for that is this.
This is where you grow.